Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: World War II (Lowell Thomas), circa 1943 - 1945; 3 (Box 1564)
    - Verso: General Henry Arnold, Colonel Howard Rusk, L.T., etc., 12-verso
    - Headquarters, Panama Canal Department, July___ -- Lowell Thomas, well-known NBC news analyst, stands with Lieut. Gen. George H. Brett, Commanding General of the Caribbean Defense Command (right), and Capt. Martin "Pete" Peterson, pilot of the "Swoose," at an airport here before making an inspection flight over the Canal. Gen. Brett personally piloted the celebrated "Swoose" while interviewed by Thomas, from the co-pilot's seat. "The war is psychologically over," the General told Thomas; 1943, 13
    - Note: Headquarters, Panama Canal Department, July___ -- Lowell Thomas, well-known NBC news analyst, stands with Lieut. Gen. George H. Brett, Commanding General of the Caribbean Defense Command (right), and Capt. Martin "Pete" Peterson, pilot of the "Swoose," at an airport here before making an inspection flight over the Canal. Gen. Brett personally piloted the celebrated "Swoose" while interviewed by Thomas, from the co-pilot's seat. "The war is psychologically over," the General told Thomas; 1943, 14
    - During participation in some war plant celebration; Spring of 1943, 15
    - Verso: During participation in some war plant celebration; Spring of 1943, 15-verso
    - In Pacific, 1945, 16
    - Note: In Pacific, 1945, 17
    - [In Pacific, 1945], 18
    - Caption: (FRANCE) - 23/4/45 - Lowell Thomas, radio commentator, gets first hand information on tactical employment of medium and light bombers from an expert - Maj. Gen. Samuel E. Anderson, Greensboro, n.C. (9th AF PHOTO - 22/4/45) Signal Corps radio telephoto from Paris. PB #859, 19
    - Lowell Thomas, noted radio commentator and war correspondent, visits the ancient Roman Ruins of Sabratha founded in the 1st Century AD. Sabratha is located near NAFD-ATC's newest and most beautiful Air Base known as Mellaha, Tripoli; 21 May 1945, 20
    - Note: Lowell Thomas, noted radio commentator and war correspondent, visits the ancient Roman Ruins of Sabratha founded in the 1st Century AD. Sabratha is located near NAFD-ATC's newest and most beautiful Air Base known as Mellaha, Tripoli; 21 May 1945, 21
    - RADIO COMMENTATOR INSPECTS ROMAN RUINS: Lowell Thomas while visiting 2000 year old ruins at Sabratha near ATC's Mellaha Air Base, Tripoli, is seen above holding bone of a Roman citizen probably buried in the 100 A.D.; 21 May 1945, 22
    - Note: RADIO COMMENTATOR INSPECTS ROMAN RUINS: Lowell Thomas while visiting 2000 year old ruins at Sabratha near ATC's Mellaha Air Base, Tripoli, is seen above holding bone of a Roman citizen probably buried in the 100 A.D.; 21 May 1945, 23
    - SO LONG UNTIL TOMORROW - Lowell Thomas, well-known radio commentator, says farewell to the beautiful ATC airbase at Mellaha, Tripoli; May 21, 1945, 24
    - Note: SO LONG UNTIL TOMORROW - Lowell Thomas, well-known radio commentator, says farewell to the beautiful ATC airbase at Mellaha, Tripoli; May 21, 1945, 25
    - Officer with Lowell Thomas, June 24, 1945 (Marianas), 26
    - Verso: Officer with Lowell Thomas, June 24, 1945 (Marianas), 26-verso
  - Subject files: World War II (Lowell Thomas), circa 1940s; 4 (Box 1564)
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others in uniform, World War II], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others in uniform, World War II], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas in military dress during World War II], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas outside of a house], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas looking through a camera, World War II], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas looking through a camera during World War II], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas filimg during World War II], 7
    - L.T. at Tripoli, Lybia[Libya], North Africa during World War II, 8
    - Verso: L.T. at Tripoli, Lybia[Libya], North Africa during World War II, 8-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man talking, World War II], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other men in military dress, World War II], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a pilot, World War II], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas eating a hot dog next to a man in a bathing suit, World War II], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other men looking at something, World War II], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas with others during World War II, signatures over respective people.], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man eating a sandwich, World War II, 15
    - [Lowell Thomas and other men gathered around a desk, World War II], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas and other men gathered around a desk, World War II], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas and other men gathered around a desk, World War II], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and others in military dress looking at a liferaft, World War II], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas and others lookingat a machine (?), World War II], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with Bob, World War II], 21
    - Note: This is Bob's envelope reaction after he solved the B.T. greatgang areab[?] they? gal., 22
  - Subject files: World War II (Lowell Thomas and Chiang Kai-shek), circa 1940s; 5 (Box 1564)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Chiang Kai-shek - General Wedemeyer cropped out of the photograph], 1
    - Note: [Lowell Thomas] with the Generalissimo and General Albert C. Wedemeyer, 2
    - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-Shek, LT, General Albert Wedemyer, 3
    - Verso: Generalissimo Chiang Kai-Shek, LT, General Albert Wedemyer, 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and General Wedemeyer with Chiang Kai-Shek], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and General Wedemeyer with Chiang Kai-Shek], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas and General Wedemeyer with Chiang Kai-Shek], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and General Wedemeyer with Chiang Kai-Shek], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and General Wedemeyer with Chiang Kai-Shek], 8
  - Subject files: World War II (Lowell Thomas and Lieutenant Colonel Richard Leghorn), 1945; 6 (Box 1564)
    - Lt. Col. Dick Leghorn officer in command of the 67th, He came from Winchester, Mass. My pilot - was Col. Karl Kraft of Clarks, Louisiana, He was number two in command of the 67th, 1
    - Note: Lt. Col. Dick Leghorn officer in command of the 67th, He came from Winchester, Mass. My pilot - was Col. Karl Kraft of Clarks, Louisiana, He was number two in command of the 67th, 2
    - Lt. Col. Dick Leghorn officer in command of the 67th, He came from Winchester, Mass. My pilot - was Col. Karl Kraft of Clarks, Louisiana, He was number two in command of the 67th, 3
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with a man in front of a plane, World War II], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas getting ready to fly in a plane, World War II], 5
    - [A pilot talking to Lowell Thomas, World War II], 6
    - [A pilot talking to Lowell Thomas, World War II], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and two pilots looking at a map, World War II], 8
    - [A pilot talking to Lowell Thomas, World War II], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and another pilot with masks on standing in front of an airplane, "Little Rebel", World War II], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting in the rear cockpit of a plane. Lt. Col. Dick Leghorn in front (?)], [3 copies], 11
  - Subject files: World War II (servicemen), circa 1942 - 1945; 7 (Box 1564)
    - SCORE CARD - Captain Donald N. Aldrich of the Marine Corps, Chicago's leading aerial ace, smiles from his fighter plane in the South Pacific. The 20 Japanese flags painted on the plane are eloquent testimony that 20 Rising Sun aircraft will rise no more. Captain Aldrich downed that many Japanese planes and won the Distinguished Flying Cross doing so. He is one of five Marine Corps aces who have shot down as many as 20 planes, 1
    - Note: SCORE CARD - Captain Donald N. Aldrich of the Marine Corps, Chicago's leading aerial ace, smiles from his fighter plane in the South Pacific. The 20 Japanese flags painted on the plane are eloquent testimony that 20 Rising Sun aircraft will rise no more. Captain Aldrich downed that many Japanese planes and won the Distinguished Flying Cross doing so. He is one of five Marine Corps aces who have shot down as many as 20 planes, 2
    - Flying Officer Robert Joseph Campbell, D.F.C., of Pawling, N.Y., who was recently awarded the Distinguished Flying Cross while serving with the Royal Canadian Air Force in Britain as an air gunner. Flying Officer Campbell, who was born in Scotland, was educated at Pawling High School and at Milford School, Milford, Connecticut. His citation reads "Flying Officer Campbell has distinguished himself by his courageous behavior, efficiency and enthusiasm for operations, which has made a notable contribution to the successes achieved by his squadron.", 3
    - Note: Flying Officer Robert Joseph Campbell, D.F.C., of Pawling, N.Y., who was recently awarded the Distinguished Flying Cross while serving with the Royal Canadian Air Force in Britain as an air gunner. Flying Officer Campbell, who was born in Scotland, was educated at Pawling High School and at Milford School, Milford, Connecticut. His citation reads "Flying Officer Campbell has distinguished himself by his courageous behavior, efficiency and enthusiasm for operations, which has made a notable contribution to the successes achieved by his squadron.", 4
    - [Sergeant Forrester L. Vosler], 5
    - [Sergeant Forrester L. Vosler], 6
    - This photograph of Gordon was made just before he left San Francisco, in 1942, 7
    - Note: This photograph of Gordon was made just before he left San Francisco, in 1942, 8
    - Gordon on Ray Steele's shoulders, 9
    - Verso: Gordon on Ray Steele's shoulders, 9-verso
    - Gordon in a potato field, 1939 (Gordon standing next to the small boy, our nephew, Robert Manuel), 10
    - Verso: Gordon in a potato field, 1939 (Gordon standing next to the small boy, our nephew, Robert Manuel), 10-verso
    - Gordon, at home, teaching our nephew, Eugene Marshall, to shoot!, 11
    - Verso: Gordon, at home, teaching our nephew, Eugene Marshall, to shoot!, 11-verso
    - Gordon on Mr. Katahdin, 1934 (Gordon at extreme left), 12
    - Verso: Gordon on Mr. Katahdin, 1934 (Gordon at extreme left), 12-verso
    - Gordon on Mt. Katahdin, 1934, 13
    - Verso: Gordon on Mt. Katahdin, 1934, 13-verso
    - Johnnie Hutchins, 14
    - Verso: THE STORY OF JOHNNIE HUTCHINS Son of a Texas sharecropper, Seaman First Class Johnnie David Hutchins, USNR, died a hero's death off Lae, New Guinea, on September 4, 1943--clinging to the wheel of LST (Landing Ship Tank) 473 after receiving a mortal wound, and using his last strength to turn the ship out of the path of a Japanese torpedo during the Allied invasion of New Guinea. He has been awarded the Medal of Honor for his bravery..., 14-verso
    - SERGEANT KELLY, THE "ONE MAN ARMY"; Sergt. Charles E. Kelly, Pittsburgh, who was taken by plane to North Africa from the U. S. Fifth Army front, to make a personal appearance on the American Expeditionary radio station's dramatization of his true story of how he killed 40 Germans at the battle of Altaville, Italy, and earned the name of the "One Man Army," of the 36th (Texas) Division, 15
    - Note: SERGEANT KELLY, THE "ONE MAN ARMY"; Sergt. Charles E. Kelly, Pittsburgh, who was taken by plane to North Africa from the U. S. Fifth Army front, to make a personal appearance on the American Expeditionary radio station's dramatization of his true story of how he killed 40 Germans at the battle of Altaville, Italy, and earned the name of the "One Man Army," of the 36th (Texas) Division, 16
    - [Major William L. Leverette] North Africa, Oct. 13, 1943; Left to right - Sprinkle, Leverette, Hanna. We three got 15 Stukas in 15 minutes a few days before, 17
    - Verso: North Africa, Oct. 13, 1943; Left to right - Sprinkle, Leverette, Hanna. We three got 15 Stukas in 15 minutes a few days before, 17-verso
    - [Major William L. Leverette] North Africa, Oc. 13, 1943; Airplane, me and one blade of prop that got too close. It flew for about 8 hours after it was gashed up before we changed it. Still ran ok, too. (Good plug for Curtiss Electric Props and Allison engines!) hadn't painted a name on plane when this was taken. Have "Stingeree" on it now. That's a fish, you know!, 18
    - Verso: North Africa, Oc. 13, 1943; Airplane, me and one blade of prop that got too close. It flew for about 8 hours after it was gashed up before we changed it. Still ran ok, too. (Good plug for Curtiss Electric Props and Allison engines!) hadn't painted a name on plane when this was taken. Have "Stingeree" on it now. That's a fish, you know!, 18-verso
    - [Major William L. Leverette] Guess who! Think that is the last starched shirt and trousers from Tallahassee!, 19
    - Verso: Guess who! Think that is the last starched shirt and trousers from Tallahassee!, 19-verso
    - [Major William L. Leverette] The prop blade I have my hand on, with the battered leading edge, is one blade of the prop I chopped a Stuka with - unintentionally! The other blade is one Lt. Sprinkle got a bullet thru - from a Stuka, 20
    - Verso: The prop blade I have my hand on, with the battered leading edge, is one blade of the prop I chopped a Stuka with - unintentionally! The other blade is one Lt. Sprinkle got a bullet thru - from a Stuka, 20-verso
    - [Major William L. Leverette], 21
    - [Major William L. Leverette], 22
    - [Major William L. Leverette], 23
    - [Major William L. Leverette], 24
    - [Lieutenant Colonel Thomas J. Lynch] Taken in New Guinea just before Tommy came home on furlough; Property of Mrs. Thomas J. Lynch, 25
    - Verso: Taken in New Guinea just before Tommy came home on furlough; Property of Mrs. Thomas J. Lynch, 25-verso
    - [Lieutenant Colonel Thomas J. Lynch] Pennsylvania Flyer Wins Four Awards; Somewhere in New Guinea - Brigadier General Ennis C. Whitehead decorates Capt. Thomas J. Lynch of Catasauqua, Pennsylvania in the field somewhere in New Guinea. Capt. Lynch received four awards: the Air Medal, D.F.C., Silver Star, and Purple Heart; Property of Mrs. Thomas J. Lynch, 26
    - Verso: Pennsylvania Flyer Wins Four Awards; Somewhere in New Guinea - Brigadier General Ennis C. Whitehead decorates Capt. Thomas J. Lynch of Catasauqua, Pennsylvania in the field somewhere in New Guinea. Capt. Lynch received four awards: the Air Medal, D.F.C., Silver Star, and Purple Heart; Property of Mrs. Thomas J. Lynch, 26-verso
    - [Lieutenant Colonel Thomas J. Lynch] Snake killed Nov. 4th; 16 feet long; "One of our little playmates"; Property of Mrs. Thomas J. Lynch, 27
    - Verso: Snake killed Nov. 4th; 16 feet long; "One of our little playmates"; Property of Mrs. Thomas J. Lynch, 27-verso
    - [Lieutenant Colonel Thomas J. Lynch] Native family that picked me up after I bailed out. June 16, 1942, 28
    - Verso: Native family that picked me up after I bailed out. June 16, 1942, 28-verso
    - [Lieutenant Colonel Thomas J. Lynch] April 1943, N.G. [New Guinea]; A few of the natives in their best [?];Property of Mrs. Thomas J. Lynch, 29
    - Verso: April 1943, N.G. [New Guinea]; A few of the natives in their best [?];Property of Mrs. Thomas J. Lynch, 29-verso
    - [Lieutenant Colonel Thomas J. Lynch] Tommy in his plane over Mr. Hagen; Property of Mrs. Thomas J. Lynch, 30
    - Verso: Tommy in his plane over Mr. Hagen; Property of Mrs. Thomas J. Lynch, 30-verso
    - [Lieutenant Colonel Thomas J. Lynch], 31
    - Verso: Thomas J. Lynch, 31-verso
    - [Major Walker M. "Bud" Mahurin] Taken just before going overseas - December 1942; Latest picture of Maj. Walker M. (Bud) Mahurin, 32
    - Verso: Taken just before going overseas - December 1942; Latest picture of Maj. Walker M. (Bud) Mahurin, 32-verso
    - [Major Walker M. "Bud" Mahurin] St. [?]; March 1943 in England, 33
    - Verso: St. [?]; March 1943 in England, 33-verso
    - [Major Walker M. "Bud" Mahurin] Luck and I again; John Truluck and Walker, 34
    - Verso: Luck and I again; John Truluck and Walker, 34-verso
    - [Major Walker M. "Bud" Mahurin] Colonel Jesse [?] giving him "The Silver Star", 35
    - Verso: Colonel Jesse [?] giving him "The Silver Star", 35-verso
    - [Major Walker M. "Bud" Mahurin] Captain Walker Mahurin shown by Paramount News, April 1944, 36
    - Verso: Captain Walker Mahurin shown by Paramount News, April 1944, 36-verso
    - [Major Walker M. "Bud" Mahurin] Paramount News picture shown April 1944, 37
    - Verso: Paramount News picture shown April 1944, 37-verso
    - [Frank J. Petraca] Frank J. Petraca, Service 1943, 38
    - Verso: Frank J. Petraca, Service 1943, 38-verso
    - [Frank J. Petraca] Pvt. Frank J, Petraraca SC 184354, 39
    - Verso: Pvt. Frank J, Petraraca SC 184354, 39-verso
    - 2nd Lieutenant Kenneth A. Walsh, USMC of 3522 Newton Street, NE, Washington, D.C., a marine fighter pilot, is running close to the record of, 40
    - Verso: 2nd Lieutenant Kenneth A. Walsh, USMC of 3522 Newton Street, NE, Washington, D.C., a marine fighter pilot, is running close to the record of, 40-verso
    - William N. [Wilbur?]; Chief of Staff, Western Defense Command, San Francisco, California, 41
    - Verso: William N. [Wilbur?]; Chief of Staff, Western Defense Command, San Francisco, California, 41-verso
    - Major "Red" Williams, 42
    - Verso: Major "Red" Williams, 42-verso
    - Sergeant Rodger W. Young, 170 Birdseye St., Clyde, Ohio, has been posthumously awarded the Congressional Medal of Honor, the Nation's highest military award, 43
    - Verso: Sergeant Rodger W. Young, 170 Birdseye St., Clyde, Ohio, has been posthumously awarded the Congressional Medal of Honor, the Nation's highest military award, 43-verso
    - TOP-FLIGHT TRIO -Ranking members of the Fighting Corsairs Marine squadron, who between them have accounted for 60 Japanese planes, are shown here. At the left is First Lieutenant Robert M. Hanson of Newtonville, Mass., who was declared missing in action after downing his 25th enemy plane, one short of the American record. In the center is Captain Harold L. Spears of Ironton, O. [Ohio], who has downed 15 planes. At the right is Captain Donald N. Aldrich of Chicago, with 20 planes to his credit. The Fighting Corsairs set five all-time Marine aviation records during their tours of duty in the South Pacific. Lieutenant Hanson and Captain Aldrich were the highest scoring pair in the squadron, 44
    - Note: TOP-FLIGHT TRIO -Ranking members of the Fighting Corsairs Marine squadron, who between them have accounted for 60 Japanese planes, are shown here. At the left is First Lieutenant Robert M. Hanson of Newtonville, Mass., who was declared missing in action after downing his 25th enemy plane, one short of the American record. In the center is Captain Harold L. Spears of Ironton, O. [Ohio], who has downed 15 planes. At the right is Captain Donald N. Aldrich of Chicago, with 20 planes to his credit. The Fighting Corsairs set five all-time Marine aviation records during their tours of duty in the South Pacific. Lieutenant Hanson and Captain Aldrich were the highest scoring pair in the squadron, 45
    - [Pilot standing in front of a plane, World War II], 46
    - [Two military personnel talking over dinner during World War II], 47
  - Subject files: World War II (servicemen - Merchant Marine Edwin F. Cheney, Jr., awarded the Maritime Distinguished Service Medal), 1942 October; 8 (Box 1564)
    - Cheney with Vice Admiral Arthur E. Fairfield - Chairman, Merchant Marine Medal Award Commettee, U.S. Maritime Commission, 1
    - Verso: Cheney with Vice Admiral Arthur E. Fairfield - Chairman, Merchant Marine Medal Award Commettee, U.S. Maritime Commission, 1-verso
    - Cheney with Rear Admiral Emory S. Land - Chairman, U.S. Maritime Commission and War Shipping Administrator, 2
    - Verso: Cheney with Rear Admiral Emory S. Land - Chairman, U.S. Maritime Commission and War Shipping Administrator, 2-verso
    - Cheney with Captain Edward Macouley - Deputy War Shipping Administrator and U.S. Maritime Commissioner, 3
    - Verso: Cheney with Captain Edward Macauley - Deputy War Shipping Administrator and U.S. Maritime Commissioner, 3-verso
    - Cheney with Captain Edward Macauley - Deputy War Shipping Administrator and U.S. Maritime Commissioner, 4
    - Verso: Cheney with Captain Edward Macauley - Deputy War Shipping Administrator and U.S. Maritime Commissioner, 4-verso
    - Cheney with Vice Admiral Arthur E. Fairfield - Chairman, Merchant Marine Medal Award Commettee, U.S. Maritime Commission, 5
    - Verso: Cheney with Vice Admiral Arthur E. Fairfield - Chairman, Merchant Marine Medal Award Commettee, U.S. Maritime Commission, 5-verso
    - [Merchant Marine Edwin F. Cheney, Jr.], 6
    - [Merchant Marine Edwin F. Cheney, Jr.], 7
    - [Maritime Distinguished Service Medal], 8
  - Subject files: World War II (miscellaneous), circa 1942 - 1945; 9 (Box 1564)
    - Observation Post, Pawling, NY; Left to right: Observer Mrs. Thomas Harvey, Chief Observer Louis P. Lemee, Observer Miss Christina Burns (sister of Major General James H. Burns), 1
    - Verso: Observation Post, Pawling, NY; Left to right: Observer Mrs. Thomas Harvey, Chief Observer Louis P. Lemee, Observer Miss Christina Burns (sister of Major General James H. Burns), 1-verso
    - Pawling, NY; Observer - Miss Christina Burns, 2
    - Verso: Pawling, NY; Observer - Miss Christina Burns, 2-verso
    - Henry P. Taylor outside Ritz, Paris, 3
    - Verso: Henry P. Taylor outside Ritz, Paris, 3-verso
    - H. P. Taylor outside Ritz, Paris, 4
    - Verso: H. P. Taylor outside Ritz, Paris, 4-verso
    - South African colored troops and [?] colored shooting craps, Forum Romanum, 5
    - Verso: South African colored troops and [?] colored shooting craps, Forum Romanum, 5-verso
    - In courtyard of Vatican, 6
    - Verso: In courtyard of Vatican, 6-verso
    - S/Sgt Earl K. [Osborne?], Miami, Florida, Sergeant Robert J. Robinson, Dallas, Texas, ground crew for Lieutenant Bruce Carr, Union Sprs., New York; 13 June 1945, 7
    - Verso: S/Sgt Earl K. [Osborne?], Miami, Florida, Sergeant Robert J. Robinson, Dallas, Texas, ground crew for Lieutenant Bruce Carr, Union Sprs., New York; 13 June 1945, 7-verso
    - R. C. girl, Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany; Miss Charlotte Suttrell, Hastings-on-Hudson; 12 June 1945, 8
    - Verso: R. C. girl, Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany; Miss Charlotte Suttrell, Hastings-on-Hudson; 12 June 1945, 8-verso
    - Eschwegge [Eschwege], Germany; 13 June 1945, 9
    - Verso: Eschwegge [Eschwege], Germany; 13 June 1945, 9-verso
    - Airfield, Eschwegge [Eschwege], Germany; 13 June 1945, 10
    - Verso: Airfield, Eschwegge [Eschwege], Germany; 13 June 1945, 10-verso
    - Eschwegge [Eschwege], Germany; 13 June 1945, 11
    - Verso: Eschwegge [Eschwege], Germany; 13 June 1945, 11-verso
    - P.W. [prisoners of war], Gotha, Germany; 13 June 1945, 12
    - Verso: P.W. [prisoners of war], Gotha, Germany; 13 June 1945, 12-verso
    - P.W. [prisoners of war], near Gotha, Germany; 13 June 1945, 13
    - Verso: P.W. [prisoners of war], near Gotha, Germany; 13 June 1945, 13-verso
    - Near Gotha, Germany; 13 June 1945; [prisoners of war], 14
    - Verso: Near Gotha, Germany; 13 June 1945; [prisoners of war], 14-verso
    - Near Gotha, Germany; 13 June 1945; [prisoners of war], 15
    - Verso: Near Gotha, Germany; 13 June 1945; [prisoners of war], 15-verso
    - [Prisoners of war near Gotha, Germany during World War II], 16
    - [Prisoners of war near Gotha, Germany during World War II], 17
    - [Prisoners of war near Gotha, Germany during World War II], 18
    - [People gathered around to hear the news during World War II], 19
    - [Men reading newspapers during World War II with the headline: "Hitler Dead"], 20
    - [A man standing in front of the Coleseum], 21
    - [A man standing in front of the Coleseum], 22
  - Subject files: World War II (miscellaneous), circa 1942 - 1945; 10 (Box 1564)